<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="mail_template_contract_cmt_full_time_employee_appointment_letter" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Employee: CMT Full Time Employee Appointment Letter</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="hr_contract_salary.model_hr_contract_salary_offer"/>
            <field name="subject">{{ object.company_id.name }}: Job Offer</field>
            <field name="partner_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="email_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="use_default_to" eval="True"/>
            <field name="description">Sent manually when you generate a simulation link on the employee contract</field>
            <field name="body_html" type="html">
                <div style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px;">
                    <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                        <strong>Appointment Letter</strong>
                    </h3>
                    <p>
                        <span style="text-align: right; display: block;">Date: <t t-esc="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d')"/></span>
                    </p>
                    <p>To</p>

                    <p>
                        <strong><t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/></strong><br/>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.mailing_address">
                            <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.mailing_address"/><br/>
                        </t>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.permanent_address">
                            <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.permanent_address"/><br/>
                        </t>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.pincode">
                            ZIP: <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.pincode"/>
                        </t>
                    </p>
                    <p>Dear <t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/>,</p>
                    <p>We are pleased to offer you a full time employment of <strong><t t-out="object.applicant_id.job_id.name"/></strong> at <strong><t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong>
                        in its <t t-out="object.company_id.street"/><t t-out="object.company_id.street2"/><t t-esc="object.company_id.city"/>,<t t-esc="object.company_id.state_id.name"/>- <t t-esc="object.company_id.zip"/>
                        office based on the terms and conditions of employment contained in this letter. Further, your appointment will
                        be effective from the date of your joining the Company.</p>
                    <p>
                        Your employment will begin on <t t-esc="object.applicant_id.ls_date_of_joining"/>
                        and your salary will be
                        /- per annum,
                        paid in accordance with the company's payroll policies.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        You will be deputed to, located at for this role.
                    </p>

                    <!-- New mandatory certification clause -->
                    <p>
                        <strong>
                        Your CCT/CRT certification within 3 months from date of joining is mandatory
                        for full-time employment confirmation.
                        </strong><br/>
                    </p>

                    <!-- Compensation and Benefits section -->
                    <p>
                        <strong>1. Compensation and Benefits:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. Your salary structure is described in the salary stack-up sheet attached as
                        “Annexure – I” of this letter and is payable in accordance with the Company’s standard
                        payroll practice and subject to applicable withholding taxes.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. The Company has the right to modify the Compensation at any time, during the term
                        of your employment. However, any such change in the Compensation will not affect the
                        terms and conditions and the obligations and duties agreed by you in this letter.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. Your individual remuneration is a matter purely between yourself and the Company and
                        has been arrived at on the basis of your job, skill-specific background, and professional merit.
                        We expect you to maintain the details of your remuneration and any changes made thereto from
                        time to time as personal and confidential.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. Leaves &amp; Holidays: You will be entitled to Leave &amp; Holidays as applicable to your category
                        of employees, location of posting, and as per the Company’s policies from time to time.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. Increment &amp; Promotions: Your growth and increase in salary will depend solely on your
                        performance and contribution to the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. Insurance: Subject to your employment with us, the Company shall ensure that you are
                        reasonably covered under relevant health insurance policies.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        g. All payments made to you will be subject to deductions required by law including
                        deductions in respect of tax and such other deductions and/or contributions as shall be
                        required to be made pursuant to the applicable laws and policies and procedures of the Company.
                    </p>
                    <p><strong>2. Probation:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        a. You will be on internship for 3 months from your date of joining. During this period,
                        the Company may conduct evaluation(s) on functional and behavioral aspects of your role as
                        deemed fit, to ascertain the suitability of the employment.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. During this period, the engagement may be ended through a written notification, by giving
                        15 days prior notice, on either side. During such period, The Company is further entitled to
                        terminate your employment at any time by providing a notice period of 15 days, or by paying you
                        salary in lieu of notice.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. On successful completion of internship or its extension, you will be intimated in writing
                        about your confirmation of employment.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>3. Background Check:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>Your appointment is subject to the verification of your credentials, testimonials and other
                        particulars mentioned by you in your application at the time of your appointment.
                        If the particulars given by you are in any way found to be inaccurate or misleading,
                        the Company shall be entitled to terminate your employment without notice or compensation
                        in lieu thereof.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>4. Policy and Practices:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>The employment terms contained in this letter are not exhaustive. In addition to this,
                        you agree to abide by all the Company’s rules, regulations, instructions, policies, practices,
                        and procedures. Any violation, non-compliance, or breach of any of the Company policies and
                        regulations shall be considered as serious misconduct and dereliction of duty, which can call
                        for immediate termination of employment. You hereby agree to indemnify the Company for any loss
                        suffered as a consequence of a breach by you of the Company’s rules, regulations, instructions,
                        policies, practices, and procedures and/or any representation warranty and obligation contained
                        in this letter.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>5. Resignation and Termination:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. You agree and acknowledge that your employment with the Company shall be valid from the date
                        of joining and continue to be effective, unless otherwise terminated in the manner herein below.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. You are required to give a notice of a of 15 days if you wish to resign from the service of
                        the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. The Company shall be entitled to terminate the engagement by giving 15 days prior notice to
                        you. However, the Company shall have the option, in its sole discretion, to make your termination
                        effective at any time prior to the end of such notice period as long as the Company pays you the
                        full salary to which you are entitled up to the last day of such reduced notice period.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. The Company shall also be entitled to terminate with immediate effect, in the event of a just
                        cause including misconduct by you such as
                        (a) consistent non-performance of your duties/services;
                        (b) disciplinary action;
                        (c) causing damage to Company's property including without limitation to
                        data in or under the control of the Company;
                        (d) excessive uninformed absenteeism for more than 5 days and tardiness in relation to the hours of work;
                        (e) In case of such termination due reasons listed above, you shall not be entitled to receive
                        Compensation or any statutory payments in lieu of notice period to be served;
                        (f) If you cease your employment without serving notice period or if the notice period is not
                        served completely, the Company may withhold the relieving letter and the other documents,
                        may recover the equivalent amount to the salary amount that you would have accrued during
                        the notice period from you in lieu of the notice period, or even take legal action against you;
                        (g) violation of any intellectual property rights, non-compete and non-disclosure of confidential
                        information provisions, undertaking or any of the terms, conditions, policies and guidelines as
                        enumerated in this letter, Confidentiality and IP Assignment Agreement and/or in its policies,
                        and/or any other conditions specifically provided to you relating to your service with Company;
                        (h) wilful omission, negligent acts, suppression of facts, misrepresentation, any acts of fraud
                        or forgery made by you including but not limited to any criminal proceedings instituted or any
                        other legal actions (whatsoever in nature) enforced against you by any judicial and/or quasi-bodies,
                        enforcement and/or governmental/regulatory/statutory authorities;
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. You shall, following notice of termination of your employment, cooperate fully with the
                        Company in all matters relating to the completion of your pending work and the orderly transition
                        of such work to such other employees as the Company may designate.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. Upon termination of your employment, you shall forthwith deliver to the Company all materials
                        and other property of Company which may be in your possession or under your power or control and
                        also will immediately surrender to the Company all notes, data, manuals, documents, records, databases,
                        programs, blueprints, memoranda, specifications, research notes, customer lists, financial reports,
                        and all other physical forms of expression incorporating or containing the trade secrets and any other
                        confidential information, it being distinctly understood that all these writings, physical forms of
                        expression and other things are Company’s exclusive property. You acknowledge that the unauthorised
                        taking, use and / or publication of Company’s trade secrets may be a violation of applicable laws,
                        including criminal laws. You further acknowledge that the unauthorised taking, use and/or publication
                        of Company’s trade secrets could cause Company to move you in a civil action to recover whatever damages,
                        awards and attorney’s fees that are by applicable law available to it.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>6. Confidentiality:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        You agree and acknowledge that you shall execute a Non-Disclosure Agreement (“NDA”) with Company
                        and the terms of which shall be binding on you. Further, you understand that the terms and conditions
                        of the NDA shall be deemed to form, and be read and construed as, part of this Agreement.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>7. Intellectual Property Rights:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        a. You irrevocably and unconditionally, recognises, covenants, and agrees with and undertakes to
                        the Company that all Intellectual Property Rights which arise in the course of Company’s Business
                        in any manner whatsoever shall belong to, and is the sole property of the Company. Notwithstanding
                        any originality, effort and skill originating from you during the term of his/her employment hereunder
                        in relation to any Intellectual Property Rights (hereinafter referred to as “Work Product”),
                        he/she shall not, at any time, (whether during the continuance of his/her employment hereunder
                        or thereafter) have any right, title or interest in or to such Intellectual Property Rights
                        (by himself/herself or in combination with any other work) and any goodwill arising through any
                        use thereof, and that all such right, title or interest shall be vested legally and exclusively with Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. You waive all moral rights, whatsoever available anywhere in the world, towards the aforementioned
                        Intellectual Property Rights accruing to the Company’s Business and here by agrees that Company is the
                        sole owner of all such Intellectual Property Rights on any such Work Products.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. All rights and obligations under this Clause 7 in respect of Intellectual Property Rights shall
                        continue in full and stay in force after the termination of your employment with Company and shall
                        be binding upon him, his personal representatives, and legal heirs.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. You shall maintain and furnish to the Company complete and current records of all Work Products
                        and Intellectual Property Rights accruing thereto and disclose to the Company in writing any such
                        inventions/ Work Products and Intellectual Property Rights.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. In the event any such Intellectual Property Rights shall vest or shall come to vest in you at
                        any time as a result (whether directly or indirectly) of the operation of law or of anything done
                        by him/her in pursuance of his employment with the Company under the laws of India or otherwise,
                        you shall be deemed to have immediately assigned all such Intellectual Property Rights absolutely
                        to Company and prior to such assignment becoming effective, you shall hold all such Intellectual
                        Property Rights on trust absolutely for the benefit of Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. You shall forthwith upon demand execute all documents and do all such acts and things required
                        to vest or perfect any vesting of all such Intellectual Property Rights legally and exclusively
                        in Company or any nominee or assignee of Company (as the Company may direct).
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        g. For the purpose of this letter, "Intellectual Property Rights” means all present and future
                        rights conferred by statute, common law or equity in any territory in or in relation to patents,
                        rights in inventions, copyright and related rights, service marks, trade secrets, know how,
                        inventions, moral rights, database rights, rights in designs, semi-conductor topography rights,
                        trade-marks, proprietary rights, business and domain names, rights in goodwill or to sue for passing off,
                        and other similar or equivalent rights or forms of protection (whether or not registered or capable of
                        registration) and all applications (and rights to apply) for, and for renewals and extensions of,
                        any such rights as may nor or in the future exist anywhere in the world.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>8. Non-Compete, Non-Circumvent and Non-Solicit</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. During the term of your employment and for a period of one year from date of termination of your
                        employment:
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. You shall not carry on or engage in, directly or indirectly, whether as an individual,
                        through a partnership or as a shareholder, joint venture partner, collaborator, consultant,
                        advisor, contractor, director, trustee, committee member, office bearer or agent or in any
                        other manner whatsoever, whether for profit or otherwise, by himself or through any other entities,
                        any business which competes or actually circumvent or interfere with the whole or any part of the
                        business of the Company or any other business that may be commenced by the Company and/or its subsidiaries
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. You shall not solicit or take away or attempt to solicit or take away, directly or indirectly,
                        any customer or prospective customer of the Company or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates for
                        any reason and/or shall not solicit or take away or attempt to solicit or take away, directly or
                        indirectly, any employee of Company or its subsidiaries or affiliates, either for your own purposes
                        or for any other person or entity.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. You shall not join, directly or indirectly, whether on a temporary or permanent basis, with any
                        of the Company’s client, customers or competitors.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. You shall not initiate, solicit, negotiate, contract with, or enter into any business transactions,
                        agreements, or undertakings with the vendors, service providers, contractors of the Company, directly
                        or indirectly and thereby, discontinue or reduce the business relationship of such vendors or service
                        providers with the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>9. Travel and other expenses</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        You may have to undertake inter-city travel on Company’s work for which you will be reimbursed travel
                        expenses as per the Company policy applicable to you.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>10. Other Conditions</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. The Company may, for business needs, transfer you to any other office location or function of the
                        Company in India or overseas or to any of its affiliates. In such case, you shall also be bound by any
                        policy of such other office or affiliate, in existence at the date of this Employment Agreement or that
                        may be subsequently framed by the Company or the affiliate. You will also be expected to make visits and
                        travel both within India and overseas, as may be necessary for the proper discharge of your duties.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. The Company expects you to work with a high standard of initiative, efficiency, and economy.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. You will be responsible for the safekeeping and return in good condition and order all the property
                        of the Company which is in your possession, use, or custody. You shall make good of any loss or damage
                        that occurs to any Company property which is in your possession/custody.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. You will be true and faithful to the Company in all your accounts, dealings and transactions relating
                        to the business of the Company and if called upon, shall render a true and just account thereof to the
                        Company or to such persons as shall be authorized to receive the same.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. This employment offer is contingent to reference check and background verification done by the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. Your employment terms may be specifically enforced legally, if required. In this connection, if any of
                        the provisions of this letter are declared or found to be void or unenforceable due to any reason whatsoever,
                        the remaining provision of this letter shall continue in full force and effect.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        g. As a standard practice, you would be required to observe 6 days’ work week, in line with your job
                        requirement. However, the working days and hours may be according to the work projects and/ or client
                        commitments and further, agrees to work on additional hours that are necessary for the proper performance
                        of the work duties. The second and fourth Saturday will be considered as holiday.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        h. You have no right or the authority to make any representation, contract, or commitment for or on
                        behalf of the Company without obtaining the prior written permission of Company in this regard.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>For <t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong></p>
                </div>
            </field>
            <field name="lang">{{ object.employee_version_id.employee_id.lang }}</field>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
        </record>

        <record id="mail_template_contract_full_time_employee_appointment_letter" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Employee: Full Time Employee Appointment Letter</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="hr_contract_salary.model_hr_contract_salary_offer"/>
            <field name="subject">{{ object.company_id.name }}: Job Offer</field>
            <field name="partner_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="email_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="use_default_to" eval="True"/>
            <field name="description">Sent manually when you generate a simulation link on the employee contract</field>
            <field name="body_html" type="html">
                <div style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px;">
                    <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                        <strong>Appointment Letter</strong>
                    </h3>
                    <p>
                        <span style="text-align: right; display: block;">Date: <t t-esc="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d')"/></span>
                    </p>
                    <p>To</p>

                    <p>
                        <strong><t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/></strong><br/>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.mailing_address">
                            <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.mailing_address"/><br/>
                        </t>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.permanent_address">
                            <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.permanent_address"/><br/>
                        </t>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.pincode">
                            ZIP: <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.pincode"/>
                        </t>
                    </p>
                    <p>Dear <t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/>,</p>
                    <p>We are pleased to offer you a full time employment of <strong><t t-out="object.applicant_id.job_id.name"/></strong> at <strong><t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong>
                        in its <t t-out="object.company_id.street"/><t t-out="object.company_id.street2"/><t t-esc="object.company_id.city"/>,<t t-esc="object.company_id.state_id.name"/>- <t t-esc="object.company_id.zip"/>
                        office based on the terms and conditions of employment contained in this letter. Further, your appointment will
                        be effective from the date of your joining the Company.</p>
                    <p>
                        Your employment will begin on <t t-esc="object.applicant_id.ls_date_of_joining"/>
                        and your salary will be
                        /- per annum,
                        paid in accordance with the company's payroll policies.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        You will be deputed to, located at for this role.
                    </p>

                    <!-- Compensation and Benefits section -->
                    <p>
                        <strong>1. Compensation and Benefits:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. Your salary structure is described in the salary stack-up sheet attached as “Annexure – I”
                        of this letter and is payable in accordance with the Company’s standard payroll practice
                        and subject to applicable withholding taxes.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b.	Your salary structure is described in the salary stack-up sheet attached as “Annexure – I”
                        of this letter and is payable in accordance with the Company’s standard payroll practice and
                        subject to applicable withholding taxes.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. Your individual remuneration is a matter purely between yourself and the Company and
                        has been arrived at the basis of your job, skill specific background and professional merit.
                        We expect you to maintain the details of your remuneration and any changes made thereto from
                        time to time as personal and confidential.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. Leaves &amp; Holidays: You will be entitled to Leave &amp; Holidays as applicable to your category
                        of employees, location of posting, and as per the Company’s policies from time to time.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. Increment &amp; Promotions: Your growth and increase in salary will depend solely on your
                        performance and contribution to the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. Insurance: Subject to your employment with us, the Company shall ensure that you are
                        reasonably covered under relevant health insurance policies.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        g. All payments made to you will be subject to deductions required by law including
                        deductions in respect of tax and such other deductions and/or contributions as shall be
                        required to be made pursuant to the applicable laws and policies and procedures of the Company.
                    </p>
                    <p><strong>2. Probation:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        a. You will be on probation for 3 months from your date of joining. During this period,
                        the Company may conduct evaluation(s) on functional and behavioral aspects of your role as
                        deemed fit, to ascertain the suitability of the employment.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. During probation period, the engagement may be ended through a written notification,
                        by giving 15 days prior notice, on either side. During such period, The Company is further
                        entitled to terminate your employment at any time by providing a notice period of 15 days,
                        or by paying you salary in lieu of notice.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. On successful completion of probation or its extension, you will be intimated in
                        writing about your confirmation of employment. Until such communication is released,
                        you shall continue to be under probation.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>3. Background Check:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>Your appointment is subject to the verification of your credentials, testimonials and other
                        particulars mentioned by you in your application at the time of your appointment. If the particulars
                        given by you are in any way found to be inaccurate or misleading, the Company shall be entitled
                        to terminate your employment without notice or compensation in lieu thereof.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>4. Policy and Practices:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>The employment terms contained in this letter are not exhaustive. In addition to this, you agree
                        to abide by all the Company’s rules, regulations, instructions, policies, practices, and procedures.
                        Any violation, non-compliance, or breach of any of the Company policies and regulations shall be
                        considered as serious misconduct and dereliction of duty, which can call for immediate termination
                        of employment. You hereby agree to indemnify the Company for any loss suffered as a consequence of
                        a breach by you of the Company’s rules, regulations, instructions, policies, practices, and procedures
                        and/or any representation warranty and obligation contained in this letter.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>5. Resignation and Termination:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. You agree and acknowledge that your employment with the Company shall be valid from the date
                        of joining and continue to be effective, unless otherwise terminated in the manner herein below.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. You are required to give a notice of a of 15 days if you wish to resign from the service of
                        the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. The Company shall be entitled to terminate the engagement by giving 15 days prior notice to
                        you. However, the Company shall have the option, in its sole discretion, to make your termination
                        effective at any time prior to the end of such notice period as long as the Company pays you the
                        full salary to which you are entitled up to the last day of such reduced notice period.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. The Company shall also be entitled to terminate with immediate effect, in the event of a just
                        cause including misconduct by you such as
                        (a) consistent non-performance of your duties/services;
                        (b) disciplinary action;
                        (c) causing damage to Company's property including without limitation to
                        data in or under the control of the Company;
                        (d) excessive uninformed absenteeism for more than 5 days and tardiness in relation to the hours of work;
                        (e) In case of such termination due reasons listed above, you shall not be entitled to receive
                        Compensation or any statutory payments in lieu of notice period to be served;
                        (f) If you cease your employment without serving notice period or if the notice period is not
                        served completely, the Company may withhold the relieving letter and the other documents,
                        may recover the equivalent amount to the salary amount that you would have accrued during
                        the notice period from you in lieu of the notice period, or even take legal action against you;
                        (g) violation of any intellectual property rights, non-compete and non-disclosure of confidential
                        information provisions, undertaking or any of the terms, conditions, policies and guidelines as
                        enumerated in this letter, Confidentiality and IP Assignment Agreement and/or in its policies,
                        and/or any other conditions specifically provided to you relating to your service with Company;
                        (h) wilful omission, negligent acts, suppression of facts, misrepresentation, any acts of fraud
                        or forgery made by you including but not limited to any criminal proceedings instituted or any
                        other legal actions (whatsoever in nature) enforced against you by any judicial and/or quasi-bodies,
                        enforcement and/or governmental/regulatory/statutory authorities;
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. You shall, following notice of termination of your employment, cooperate fully with the
                        Company in all matters relating to the completion of your pending work and the orderly transition
                        of such work to such other employees as the Company may designate.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. Upon termination of your employment, you shall forthwith deliver to the Company all materials
                        and other property of Company which may be in your possession or under your power or control and
                        also will immediately surrender to the Company all notes, data, manuals, documents, records, databases,
                        programs, blueprints, memoranda, specifications, research notes, customer lists, financial reports,
                        and all other physical forms of expression incorporating or containing the trade secrets and any other
                        confidential information, it being distinctly understood that all these writings, physical forms of
                        expression and other things are Company’s exclusive property. You acknowledge that the unauthorised
                        taking, use and / or publication of Company’s trade secrets may be a violation of applicable laws,
                        including criminal laws. You further acknowledge that the unauthorised taking, use and/or publication
                        of Company’s trade secrets could cause Company to move you in a civil action to recover whatever damages,
                        awards and attorney’s fees that are by applicable law available to it.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>6. Confidentiality:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        You agree and acknowledge that you shall execute a Non-Disclosure Agreement (“NDA”) with Company
                        and the terms of which shall be binding on you. Further, you understand that the terms and conditions
                        of the NDA shall be deemed to form, and be read and construed as, part of this Agreement.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>7. Intellectual Property Rights:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        a. You irrevocably and unconditionally, recognises, covenants, and agrees with and undertakes to
                        the Company that all Intellectual Property Rights which arise in the course of Company’s Business
                        in any manner whatsoever shall belong to, and is the sole property of the Company. Notwithstanding
                        any originality, effort and skill originating from you during the term of his/her employment hereunder
                        in relation to any Intellectual Property Rights (hereinafter referred to as “Work Product”),
                        he/she shall not, at any time, (whether during the continuance of his/her employment hereunder
                        or thereafter) have any right, title or interest in or to such Intellectual Property Rights
                        (by himself/herself or in combination with any other work) and any goodwill arising through any
                        use thereof, and that all such right, title or interest shall be vested legally and exclusively with Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. You waive all moral rights, whatsoever available anywhere in the world, towards the aforementioned
                        Intellectual Property Rights accruing to the Company’s Business and here by agrees that Company is the
                        sole owner of all such Intellectual Property Rights on any such Work Products.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. All rights and obligations under this Clause 7 in respect of Intellectual Property Rights shall
                        continue in full and stay in force after the termination of your employment with Company and shall
                        be binding upon him, his personal representatives, and legal heirs.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. You shall maintain and furnish to the Company complete and current records of all Work Products
                        and Intellectual Property Rights accruing thereto and disclose to the Company in writing any such
                        inventions/ Work Products and Intellectual Property Rights.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. In the event any such Intellectual Property Rights shall vest or shall come to vest in you at
                        any time as a result (whether directly or indirectly) of the operation of law or of anything done
                        by him/her in pursuance of his employment with the Company under the laws of India or otherwise,
                        you shall be deemed to have immediately assigned all such Intellectual Property Rights absolutely
                        to Company and prior to such assignment becoming effective, you shall hold all such Intellectual
                        Property Rights on trust absolutely for the benefit of Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. You shall forthwith upon demand execute all documents and do all such acts and things required
                        to vest or perfect any vesting of all such Intellectual Property Rights legally and exclusively
                        in Company or any nominee or assignee of Company (as the Company may direct).
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        g. For the purpose of this letter, "Intellectual Property Rights” means all present and future
                        rights conferred by statute, common law or equity in any territory in or in relation to patents,
                        rights in inventions, copyright and related rights, service marks, trade secrets, know how,
                        inventions, moral rights, database rights, rights in designs, semi-conductor topography rights,
                        trade-marks, proprietary rights, business and domain names, rights in goodwill or to sue for passing off,
                        and other similar or equivalent rights or forms of protection (whether or not registered or capable of
                        registration) and all applications (and rights to apply) for, and for renewals and extensions of,
                        any such rights as may nor or in the future exist anywhere in the world.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>8. Non-Compete, Non-Circumvent and Non-Solicit</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. During the term of your employment and for a period of one year from date of termination of your
                        employment:
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. You shall not carry on or engage in, directly or indirectly, whether as an individual,
                        through a partnership or as a shareholder, joint venture partner, collaborator, consultant,
                        advisor, contractor, director, trustee, committee member, office bearer or agent or in any
                        other manner whatsoever, whether for profit or otherwise, by himself or through any other entities,
                        any business which competes or actually circumvent or interfere with the whole or any part of the
                        business of the Company or any other business that may be commenced by the Company and/or its subsidiaries
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. You shall not solicit or take away or attempt to solicit or take away, directly or indirectly,
                        any customer or prospective customer of the Company or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates for
                        any reason and/or shall not solicit or take away or attempt to solicit or take away, directly or
                        indirectly, any employee of Company or its subsidiaries or affiliates, either for your own purposes
                        or for any other person or entity.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. You shall not join, directly or indirectly, whether on a temporary or permanent basis, with any
                        of the Company’s client, customers or competitors.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. You shall not initiate, solicit, negotiate, contract with, or enter into any business transactions,
                        agreements, or undertakings with the vendors, service providers, contractors of the Company, directly
                        or indirectly and thereby, discontinue or reduce the business relationship of such vendors or service
                        providers with the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>9. Travel and other expenses</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        You may have to undertake inter-city travel on Company’s work for which you will be reimbursed travel
                        expenses as per the Company policy applicable to you.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>10. Other Conditions</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. The Company may, for business needs, transfer you to any other office location or function of the
                        Company in India or overseas or to any of its affiliates. In such case, you shall also be bound by any
                        policy of such other office or affiliate, in existence at the date of this Employment Agreement or that
                        may be subsequently framed by the Company or the affiliate. You will also be expected to make visits and
                        travel both within India and overseas, as may be necessary for the proper discharge of your duties.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. The Company expects you to work with a high standard of initiative, efficiency, and economy.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. You will be responsible for the safekeeping and return in good condition and order all the property
                        of the Company which is in your possession, use, or custody. You shall make good of any loss or damage
                        that occurs to any Company property which is in your possession/custody.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. You will be true and faithful to the Company in all your accounts, dealings and transactions relating
                        to the business of the Company and if called upon, shall render a true and just account thereof to the
                        Company or to such persons as shall be authorized to receive the same.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. This employment offer is contingent to reference check and background verification done by the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. Your employment terms may be specifically enforced legally, if required. In this connection, if any of
                        the provisions of this letter are declared or found to be void or unenforceable due to any reason whatsoever,
                        the remaining provision of this letter shall continue in full force and effect.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        g. As a standard practice, you would be required to observe 6 days’ work week, in line with your job
                        requirement. However, the working days and hours may be according to the work projects and/ or client
                        commitments and further, agrees to work on additional hours that are necessary for the proper performance
                        of the work duties. The second and fourth Saturday will be considered as holiday.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        h. You have no right or the authority to make any representation, contract, or commitment for or on
                        behalf of the Company without obtaining the prior written permission of Company in this regard.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>For <t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong></p>

                    <div style="page-break-before: always; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;">

                        <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                            <strong>Annexure I</strong>
                        </h3>

                        <!-- Employee Details -->
                        <p>Name: </p>
                        <p>Designation: </p>
                        <p>Band: </p>
                        <p>Level: </p>
                        <p>Date of joining:</p>

                        <br/>

                        <p>The breakup of the Salary is given below:</p>

                        <!-- Salary Table -->
                        <table style="width: 80%; border-collapse: collapse; margin-top: 10px;">
                            <thead>
                                <tr>
                                    <th style="padding: 8px; text-align: left; border: 1px solid black;">Particulars</th>
                                    <th style="padding: 8px; text-align: left; border: 1px solid black;">Monthly</th>
                                    <th style="padding: 8px; text-align: left; border: 1px solid black;">Annual CTC</th>
                                </tr>
                            </thead>
                            <tbody>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">Basic Pay + DA</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">HRA</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">Special Allowance</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;"><strong>Total Gross Pay</strong></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">Employer PF</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;"><strong>CTC</strong></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                            </tbody>
                        </table>
                        <br/>

                        <!-- Notes -->
                        <ul style="margin-top: 15px;">
                            <li>
                                Taxation: The Income Tax Act as prevailing at the time of employment,
                                will govern the taxation matters. The Company will deduct tax at source
                                as per the prevailing income tax law.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                Gratuity and Insurance is over and above CTC.
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </div>
                    <div style="page-break-before: always; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;">

                        <!-- Title -->
                        <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                            <strong>ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE</strong>
                        </h3>

                        <!-- Paragraph -->
                        <p style="text-align: justify; line-height: 1.6;">
                            I have read and understood thoroughly the rules of employment/obligations of my employment
                            contained herein and all the terms of appointment of my employment, and I do hereby agree with all
                            terms as above and I shall abide by all general rules of employment/service which are now or may
                            hereafter to be in force, and accordingly I accept the appointment of my employment with you.
                            Upon acceptance and execution, this letter will constitute the legally binding and enforceable
                            employment agreement between self and Company.
                        </p>

                        <br/><br/>

                        <p>Signature: ______________________</p>
                        <p>Name: ______________________</p>
                        <p>Date: ______________________</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </field>
            <field name="lang">{{ object.employee_version_id.employee_id.lang }}</field>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
        </record>

        <record id="mail_template_contract_hse_appointment_letter" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Employee: HSE Appointment Letter</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="hr_contract_salary.model_hr_contract_salary_offer"/>
            <field name="subject">{{ object.company_id.name }}: Job Offer</field>
            <field name="partner_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="email_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="use_default_to" eval="True"/>
            <field name="description">Sent manually when you generate a simulation link on the employee contract</field>
            <field name="body_html" type="html">
                <div style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px;">

                    <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                        <strong>Appointment Letter</strong>
                    </h3>

                    <p>
                        <span style="text-align: right; display: block;">Date: <t t-esc="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d')"/></span>
                    </p>
                    <p>To</p>

                    <p>
                        <strong><t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/></strong><br/>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.mailing_address">
                            <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.mailing_address"/><br/>
                        </t>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.permanent_address">
                            <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.permanent_address"/><br/>
                        </t>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.pincode">
                            ZIP: <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.pincode"/>
                        </t>
                    </p>
                    <p>Dear <t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/>,</p>
                    <p>We are pleased to offer you a full time employment of <strong><t t-out="object.applicant_id.job_id.name"/></strong> at <strong><t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong>
                        in its <t t-out="object.company_id.street"/><t t-out="object.company_id.street2"/><t t-esc="object.company_id.city"/>,<t t-esc="object.company_id.state_id.name"/>- <t t-esc="object.company_id.zip"/>
                        office based on the terms and conditions of employment contained in this letter. Further, your appointment will
                        be effective from the date of your joining the Company.</p>
                    <p>
                        Your employment will begin on <t t-esc="object.applicant_id.ls_date_of_joining"/>
                        and your salary will be
                        /- per annum,
                        paid in accordance with the company's payroll policies.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        You will be deputed to, located at for this role.
                    </p>

                    <!-- Compensation and Benefits section -->
                    <p>
                        <strong>1. Compensation and Benefits:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. Your salary structure is described in the salary stack-up sheet attached as “Annexure – I” of this letter and is payable in accordance with the Company’s standard payroll practice and subject to applicable withholding taxes.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b.	The Company has the right to modify the Compensation at any time, during the term of your employment. However, any such change in the Compensation will not affect the terms and conditions and the obligations and duties agreed by you in this letter.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c.	Your individual remuneration is a matter purely between yourself and the Company and has been arrived at the basis of your job, skill specific background and professional merit. We expect you to maintain the details of your remuneration and any changes made thereto from time to time as personal and confidential.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. Leaves &amp; Holidays: You will be entitled to Leave &amp; Holidays as applicable to your category
                        of employees, location of posting, and as per the Company’s policies from time to time.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. Increment &amp; Promotions: Your growth and increase in salary will depend solely on your
                        performance and contribution to the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. Insurance: Subject to your employment with us, the Company shall ensure that you are
                        reasonably covered under relevant health insurance policies.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        g. All payments made to you will be subject to deductions required by law including
                        deductions in respect of tax and such other deductions and/or contributions as shall be
                        required to be made pursuant to the applicable laws and policies and procedures of the Company.
                    </p>
                    <p><strong>2. Probation:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        a. You will be on probation for 3 months from your date of joining. During this period,
                        the Company may conduct evaluation(s) on functional and behavioral aspects of your role as
                        deemed fit, to ascertain the suitability of the employment.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. During probation period, the engagement may be ended through a written notification,
                        by giving 15 days prior notice, on either side. During such period, The Company is further
                        entitled to terminate your employment at any time by providing a notice period of 15 days,
                        or by paying you salary in lieu of notice.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c.	On successful completion of internship or its extension, you will be intimated in writing about your confirmation of employment.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>3. Background Check:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>Your appointment is subject to the verification of your credentials, testimonials and other particulars mentioned by you in your application at the time of your appointment. If the particulars given by you are in any way found to be inaccurate or misleading, the Company shall be entitled to terminate your employment without notice or compensation in lieu thereof.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>4. Policy and Practices:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>The employment terms contained in this letter are not exhaustive. In addition to this, you agree
                        to abide by all the Company’s rules, regulations, instructions, policies, practices, and procedures.
                        Any violation, non-compliance, or breach of any of the Company policies and regulations shall be
                        considered as serious misconduct and dereliction of duty, which can call for immediate termination
                        of employment. You hereby agree to indemnify the Company for any loss suffered as a consequence of
                        a breach by you of the Company’s rules, regulations, instructions, policies, practices, and procedures
                        and/or any representation warranty and obligation contained in this letter.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>5. Resignation and Termination:</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. You agree and acknowledge that your employment with the Company shall be valid from the date
                        of joining and continue to be effective, unless otherwise terminated in the manner herein below.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. You are required to give a notice of a of 15 days if you wish to resign from the service of
                        the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. The Company shall be entitled to terminate the engagement by giving 15 days prior notice to
                        you. However, the Company shall have the option, in its sole discretion, to make your termination
                        effective at any time prior to the end of such notice period as long as the Company pays you the
                        full salary to which you are entitled up to the last day of such reduced notice period.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. The Company shall also be entitled to terminate with immediate effect, in the event of a just
                        cause including misconduct by you such as
                        (a) consistent non-performance of your duties/services;
                        (b) disciplinary action;
                        (c) causing damage to Company's property including without limitation to
                        data in or under the control of the Company;
                        (d) excessive uninformed absenteeism for more than 5 days and tardiness in relation to the hours of work;
                        (e) In case of such termination due reasons listed above, you shall not be entitled to receive
                        Compensation or any statutory payments in lieu of notice period to be served;
                        (f) If you cease your employment without serving notice period or if the notice period is not
                        served completely, the Company may withhold the relieving letter and the other documents,
                        may recover the equivalent amount to the salary amount that you would have accrued during
                        the notice period from you in lieu of the notice period, or even take legal action against you;
                        (g) violation of any intellectual property rights, non-compete and non-disclosure of confidential
                        information provisions, undertaking or any of the terms, conditions, policies and guidelines as
                        enumerated in this letter, Confidentiality and IP Assignment Agreement and/or in its policies,
                        and/or any other conditions specifically provided to you relating to your service with Company;
                        (h) wilful omission, negligent acts, suppression of facts, misrepresentation, any acts of fraud
                        or forgery made by you including but not limited to any criminal proceedings instituted or any
                        other legal actions (whatsoever in nature) enforced against you by any judicial and/or quasi-bodies,
                        enforcement and/or governmental/regulatory/statutory authorities;
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. You shall, following notice of termination of your employment, cooperate fully with the
                        Company in all matters relating to the completion of your pending work and the orderly transition
                        of such work to such other employees as the Company may designate.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. Upon termination of your employment, you shall forthwith deliver to the Company all materials
                        and other property of Company which may be in your possession or under your power or control and
                        also will immediately surrender to the Company all notes, data, manuals, documents, records, databases,
                        programs, blueprints, memoranda, specifications, research notes, customer lists, financial reports,
                        and all other physical forms of expression incorporating or containing the trade secrets and any other
                        confidential information, it being distinctly understood that all these writings, physical forms of
                        expression and other things are Company’s exclusive property. You acknowledge that the unauthorised
                        taking, use and / or publication of Company’s trade secrets may be a violation of applicable laws,
                        including criminal laws. You further acknowledge that the unauthorised taking, use and/or publication
                        of Company’s trade secrets could cause Company to move you in a civil action to recover whatever damages,
                        awards and attorney’s fees that are by applicable law available to it.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>6. Confidentiality:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        You agree and acknowledge that you shall execute a Non-Disclosure Agreement (“NDA”) with Company
                        and the terms of which shall be binding on you. Further, you understand that the terms and conditions
                        of the NDA shall be deemed to form, and be read and construed as, part of this Agreement.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>7. Intellectual Property Rights:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        a. You irrevocably and unconditionally, recognises, covenants, and agrees with and undertakes to
                        the Company that all Intellectual Property Rights which arise in the course of Company’s Business
                        in any manner whatsoever shall belong to, and is the sole property of the Company. Notwithstanding
                        any originality, effort and skill originating from you during the term of his/her employment hereunder
                        in relation to any Intellectual Property Rights (hereinafter referred to as “Work Product”),
                        he/she shall not, at any time, (whether during the continuance of his/her employment hereunder
                        or thereafter) have any right, title or interest in or to such Intellectual Property Rights
                        (by himself/herself or in combination with any other work) and any goodwill arising through any
                        use thereof, and that all such right, title or interest shall be vested legally and exclusively with Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. You waive all moral rights, whatsoever available anywhere in the world, towards the aforementioned
                        Intellectual Property Rights accruing to the Company’s Business and here by agrees that Company is the
                        sole owner of all such Intellectual Property Rights on any such Work Products.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. All rights and obligations under this Clause 7 in respect of Intellectual Property Rights shall
                        continue in full and stay in force after the termination of your employment with Company and shall
                        be binding upon him, his personal representatives, and legal heirs.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. You shall maintain and furnish to the Company complete and current records of all Work Products
                        and Intellectual Property Rights accruing thereto and disclose to the Company in writing any such
                        inventions/ Work Products and Intellectual Property Rights.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. In the event any such Intellectual Property Rights shall vest or shall come to vest in you at
                        any time as a result (whether directly or indirectly) of the operation of law or of anything done
                        by him/her in pursuance of his employment with the Company under the laws of India or otherwise,
                        you shall be deemed to have immediately assigned all such Intellectual Property Rights absolutely
                        to Company and prior to such assignment becoming effective, you shall hold all such Intellectual
                        Property Rights on trust absolutely for the benefit of Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. You shall forthwith upon demand execute all documents and do all such acts and things required
                        to vest or perfect any vesting of all such Intellectual Property Rights legally and exclusively
                        in Company or any nominee or assignee of Company (as the Company may direct).
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        g. For the purpose of this letter, "Intellectual Property Rights” means all present and future
                        rights conferred by statute, common law or equity in any territory in or in relation to patents,
                        rights in inventions, copyright and related rights, service marks, trade secrets, know how,
                        inventions, moral rights, database rights, rights in designs, semi-conductor topography rights,
                        trade-marks, proprietary rights, business and domain names, rights in goodwill or to sue for passing off,
                        and other similar or equivalent rights or forms of protection (whether or not registered or capable of
                        registration) and all applications (and rights to apply) for, and for renewals and extensions of,
                        any such rights as may nor or in the future exist anywhere in the world.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>8. Non-Compete, Non-Circumvent and Non-Solicit</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. During the term of your employment and for a period of one year from date of termination of your
                        employment:
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. You shall not carry on or engage in, directly or indirectly, whether as an individual,
                        through a partnership or as a shareholder, joint venture partner, collaborator, consultant,
                        advisor, contractor, director, trustee, committee member, office bearer or agent or in any
                        other manner whatsoever, whether for profit or otherwise, by himself or through any other entities,
                        any business which competes or actually circumvent or interfere with the whole or any part of the
                        business of the Company or any other business that may be commenced by the Company and/or its subsidiaries
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. You shall not solicit or take away or attempt to solicit or take away, directly or indirectly,
                        any customer or prospective customer of the Company or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates for
                        any reason and/or shall not solicit or take away or attempt to solicit or take away, directly or
                        indirectly, any employee of Company or its subsidiaries or affiliates, either for your own purposes
                        or for any other person or entity.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. You shall not join, directly or indirectly, whether on a temporary or permanent basis, with any
                        of the Company’s client, customers or competitors.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. You shall not initiate, solicit, negotiate, contract with, or enter into any business transactions,
                        agreements, or undertakings with the vendors, service providers, contractors of the Company, directly
                        or indirectly and thereby, discontinue or reduce the business relationship of such vendors or service
                        providers with the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>9. Travel and other expenses</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        You may have to undertake inter-city travel on Company’s work for which you will be reimbursed travel
                        expenses as per the Company policy applicable to you.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <strong>10. Other Conditions</strong>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        a. The Company may, for business needs, transfer you to any other office location or function of the
                        Company in India or overseas or to any of its affiliates. In such case, you shall also be bound by any
                        policy of such other office or affiliate, in existence at the date of this Employment Agreement or that
                        may be subsequently framed by the Company or the affiliate. You will also be expected to make visits and
                        travel both within India and overseas, as may be necessary for the proper discharge of your duties.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        b. The Company expects you to work with a high standard of initiative, efficiency, and economy.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        c. You will be responsible for the safekeeping and return in good condition and order all the property
                        of the Company which is in your possession, use, or custody. You shall make good of any loss or damage
                        that occurs to any Company property which is in your possession/custody.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        d. You will be true and faithful to the Company in all your accounts, dealings and transactions relating
                        to the business of the Company and if called upon, shall render a true and just account thereof to the
                        Company or to such persons as shall be authorized to receive the same.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        e. This employment offer is contingent to reference check and background verification done by the Company.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        f. Your employment terms may be specifically enforced legally, if required. In this connection, if any of
                        the provisions of this letter are declared or found to be void or unenforceable due to any reason whatsoever,
                        the remaining provision of this letter shall continue in full force and effect.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        g. As a standard practice, you would be required to observe 6 days’ work week, in line with your job
                        requirement. However, the working days and hours may be according to the work projects and/ or client
                        commitments and further, agrees to work on additional hours that are necessary for the proper performance
                        of the work duties. The second and fourth Saturday will be considered as holiday.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        h. You have no right or the authority to make any representation, contract, or commitment for or on
                        behalf of the Company without obtaining the prior written permission of Company in this regard.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>For <t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong></p>

                    <div style="page-break-before: always; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;">

                        <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                            <strong>Annexure I</strong>
                        </h3>

                        <!-- Employee Details -->
                        <p>Name: </p>
                        <p>Designation: </p>
                        <p>Band: </p>
                        <p>Level: </p>
                        <p>Date of joining:</p>

                        <br/>

                        <p>The breakup of the Salary is given below:</p>

                        <!-- Salary Table -->
                        <table style="width: 80%; border-collapse: collapse; margin-top: 10px;">
                            <thead>
                                <tr>
                                    <th style="padding: 8px; text-align: left; border: 1px solid black;">Particulars</th>
                                    <th style="padding: 8px; text-align: left; border: 1px solid black;">Monthly</th>
                                    <th style="padding: 8px; text-align: left; border: 1px solid black;">Annual CTC</th>
                                </tr>
                            </thead>
                            <tbody>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">Basic Pay + DA</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">HRA</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">Special Allowance</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;"><strong>Total Gross Pay</strong></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">Employer PF</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;"><strong>CTC</strong></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                            </tbody>
                        </table>
                        <br/>

                        <!-- Notes -->
                        <ul style="margin-top: 15px;">
                            <li>
                                Taxation: The Income Tax Act as prevailing at the time of employment,
                                will govern the taxation matters. The Company will deduct tax at source
                                as per the prevailing income tax law.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                Gratuity and Insurance is over and above CTC.
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </div>
                    <div style="page-break-before: always; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;">

                        <!-- Title -->
                        <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                            <strong>ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE</strong>
                        </h3>

                        <!-- Paragraph -->
                        <p style="text-align: justify; line-height: 1.6;">
                            I have read and understood thoroughly the rules of employment/obligations of my employment
                            contained herein and all the terms of appointment of my employment, and I do hereby agree with all
                            terms as above and I shall abide by all general rules of employment/service which are now or may
                            hereafter to be in force, and accordingly I accept the appointment of my employment with you.
                            Upon acceptance and execution, this letter will constitute the legally binding and enforceable
                            employment agreement between self and Company.
                        </p>

                        <br/><br/>

                        <p>Signature: ______________________</p>
                        <p>Name: ______________________</p>
                        <p>Date: ______________________</p>
                    </div>

                </div>
            </field>
            <field name="lang">{{ object.employee_version_id.employee_id.lang }}</field>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
        </record>

<!--        Fulltime employee offer letter template-->
        <record id="mail_template_full_time_employee_offer_letter_template" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Employee: Full Time Employee Offer Letter</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="hr_contract_salary.model_hr_contract_salary_offer"/>
            <field name="subject">{{ object.company_id.name }}: Job Offer</field>
            <field name="partner_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="email_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="use_default_to" eval="True"/>
            <field name="description">Sent manually when you generate a simulation link on the employee contract</field>
            <field name="body_html" type="html">
                <div style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px;">

                    <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                        <strong>Offer of Appointment</strong>
                    </h3>

                    <p>
                        <span style="text-align: right; display: block;">Date: <t t-esc="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d')"/></span>
                    </p>
                    <p>To</p>

                    <p>
                        <strong><t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/></strong><br/>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.permanent_address">
                            <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.permanent_address"/><br/>
                        </t>

                    </p>
                    <p>Dear <t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/>,</p>
                    <p>We are pleased to offer you a position with <strong><t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong>
                        in its <t t-out="object.company_id.street"/><t t-out="object.company_id.street2"/><t t-esc="object.company_id.city"/>,<t t-esc="object.company_id.state_id.name"/>- <t t-esc="object.company_id.zip"/>
                        on the following terms and conditions:
                    </p>
                    <ol>
                        <li>
                            <strong><t t-esc="object.applicant_id.job_id.name"/></strong>
                        </li>

                        <li>
                            <strong><t t-esc="object.applicant_id.job_id.name"/></strong>
                        </li>

                        <li>
                            We would appreciate you joining us on or before
                            <strong><t t-esc="object.applicant_id.ls_date_of_joining"/></strong>.
                        </li>

                        <li>
                            Compensation: Your Annual Compensation will be INR
                             CTC Per Annum,
                            including a Variable Pay INR
                            Annexure 1 outlines the detailed component-wise stack up.
                        </li>

                        <li>
                            You will be deputed to
                            located at
                            for this role.
                        </li>
                    </ol>

                    <p>
                        The Company may, for business needs, may change your reporting manager, or transfer you
                        to any other office location or function of the Company in India or overseas or to any
                        of its affiliates.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        <i>
                            The offer stands automatically revoked, not joining as per the indicated timelines.
                            Discussions or attempts to arrive at a revised joining date could be made, but in case
                            no agreement on a date is arrived at, the date indicated in the offer (or last agreed in writing thereafter)
                            would be considered as the date by which the you should join, failing which the offer would automatically
                            stand revoked. While you are at liberty to reject the offer by indicating in writing, the offer can also be revoked
                            at the discretion of the management, before your date of joining.
                        </i>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        Acceptance: Your formal acceptance of the terms &amp; conditions of this offer should be confirmed in
                        writing (reply to email/countersigning this Offer Letter) within 3 calendar days.
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>Terms and Conditions of Association:</strong></p>

                    <p>
                        Verification: This offer may be subject to a positive reference check and background screening.
                        In the event that background verification has not been completed to the satisfaction of the Company
                        in its sole discretion or you have been found to have willfully suppressed or forged any piece of
                        information during the course of the interview or employment, the Company reserves the right to cancel
                        this offer letter and terminate any subsequent agreement with immediate effect with written notice to that effect.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        Probation, Confirmation, and Notice period You will be on probation for a period of 3 months. During this
                        period, the Company may conduct evaluation(s) on functional and behavioral aspects of your role as deemed
                        fit, to ascertain the suitability of the employment.

                    </p>
                    <p>
                        During probation, the employment may be ended through a written notification, by giving 15 days’ notice, on
                        either side. The  Company shall be entitled to terminate your employment at any time by paying you a salary in lieu of notice.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        As a confirmed employee, the employment can be terminated by giving 15 days’ notice, on either side.
                        The  Company shall be entitled to terminate your engagement at any time by paying you a salary in lieu of notice.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        A detailed agreement outlining the terms and conditions of your association with the Company will be issued
                        as part of your joining formalities. During the course of employment with the company, you shall not enter
                        the service or employment, consultancy, full or part time, for any other person or organization, nor shall you
                        carry on or be interested in any business.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        You will be governed by the policies of the company as may be applicable from time to time.
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        Your compensation details are personal and must be treated with absolute confidentiality
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        Documents: On the date of joining, please provide self-attested and dated copies of below (digital version accepted):
                    </p>

                    <ul style="margin-top: 10px;">
                        <li>Aadhar card</li>
                        <li>PAN card</li>
                        <li>Driving license (if available)</li>
                        <li>Current / latest employment: Acceptance of Resignation / Relieving letter</li>
                        <li>Previous employment: Experience letters, relieving letters</li>
                        <li>Educational certificates and mark sheets (Degree/Diploma, X and XII)</li>
                        <li>Passport-sized photographs</li>
                    </ul>

                    <p>
                        Looking forward to having you on board and together creating a story!
                    </p>

                    <p><strong>For <t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong></p>

                    <div style="page-break-before: always; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;">

                        <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                            <strong>Annexure I</strong>
                        </h3>

                        <!-- Employee Details -->
                        <p>Name: </p>
                        <p>Designation: </p>
                        <p>Band: </p>
                        <p>Level: </p>
                        <p>Date of joining:</p>

                        <br/>

                        <p>The breakup of the Salary is given below:</p>

                        <!-- Salary Table -->
                        <table style="width: 80%; border-collapse: collapse; margin-top: 10px;">
                            <thead>
                                <tr>
                                    <th style="padding: 8px; text-align: left; border: 1px solid black;">Particulars</th>
                                    <th style="padding: 8px; text-align: left; border: 1px solid black;">Monthly</th>
                                    <th style="padding: 8px; text-align: left; border: 1px solid black;">Annual CTC</th>
                                </tr>
                            </thead>
                            <tbody>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">Basic Pay + DA</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">HRA</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">Special Allowance</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;"><strong>Total Gross Pay</strong></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;">Employer PF</td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="padding: 6px; border: 1px solid black;"><strong>CTC</strong></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                    <td style="border: 1px solid black;"></td>
                                </tr>
                            </tbody>
                        </table>
                        <br/>

                        <!-- Notes -->
                        <ul style="margin-top: 15px;">
                            <li>
                                Taxation: The Income Tax Act as prevailing at the time of employment,
                                will govern the taxation matters. The Company will deduct tax at source
                                as per the prevailing income tax law.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                Gratuity and Insurance is over and above CTC.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                If Variable Performance Pay is included: Payable annually with outcomes be measured
                                against clearly defined and mutually agreed goals, reviewed monthly with manager.
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </field>
            <field name="lang">{{ object.employee_version_id.employee_id.lang }}</field>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
        </record>

<!--        Internship offer template-->

        <record id="mail_template_internship_offer_template" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Employee: Internship Offer Template</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="hr_contract_salary.model_hr_contract_salary_offer"/>
            <field name="subject">{{ object.company_id.name }}: Job Offer</field>
            <field name="partner_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="email_to" eval="False"/>
            <field name="use_default_to" eval="True"/>
            <field name="description">Sent manually when you generate a simulation link on the employee contract</field>
            <field name="body_html" type="html">
                <div style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px;">

                    <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline; margin-bottom: 20px;">
                        <strong>Internship Letter</strong>
                    </h3>

                    <p>
                        <span style="text-align: right; display: block;">Date: <t t-esc="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d')"/></span>
                    </p>
                    <p>To</p>

                    <p>
                        <strong><t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/></strong><br/>

                        <t t-if="object.applicant_id.permanent_address">
                            <span t-esc="object.applicant_id.permanent_address"/><br/>
                        </t>

                    </p>
                    <p>Dear <t t-out="object.applicant_id.partner_name"/>,</p>
                    <h3 style="margin-bottom: 20px;">
                        <strong>OFFER FOR INTERNSHIP WITH <t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong>
                    </h3>
                    <p>We are pleased to offer you an internship with <strong><t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong>.,
                        This internship will be based in on the following terms and conditions.
                    </p>
                    <div style="margin-top: 15px; font-family: Arial;">

                        <p><strong>1. Duration of Internship</strong></p>
                        <p style="margin-left: 20px;">
                            The duration of internship shall be from
                        </p>

                        <p><strong>2. Working Days</strong></p>
                        <p style="margin-left: 20px;">
                            6 working days in a week. Second and fourth Saturday will be considered as holiday.
                        </p>

                        <p><strong>3. Stipend</strong></p>
                        <p style="margin-left: 20px;">
                            You shall be paid a monthly stipend of INR
                        </p>

                        <p><strong>4. Confidentiality</strong></p>
                        <p style="margin-left: 20px; text-align: justify;">
                            You will undertake to keep all information pertaining to the company strictly confidential,
                            and you will not divulge any such information to anyone outside the Company.
                        </p>

                        <p><strong>5. Terms and Conditions of Association</strong></p>
                        <ol type="i" style="margin-left: 40px;">
                            <li>
                                During the course of internship with the company, you shall not enter into any employment,
                                consultancy (full-time or part-time), nor engage in any other business.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                You will be governed by the policies of the company as applicable from time to time.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                Your stipend details are personal and must be treated with absolute confidentiality.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                You are required to provide a notice of 15 days if you wish to end the internship period.
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                The Company reserves the right to terminate the internship by providing fifteen (15) days’
                                prior written notice.
                            </li>
                        </ol>

                        <p><strong>6. Documents</strong></p>
                        <p style="margin-left: 20px;">
                            On the date of joining, please provide self-attested and dated copies of:
                        </p>

                        <ol type="i" style="margin-left: 40px;">
                            <li>
                                Mandatory: Bonafide letter from college (approval for internship or bonafide certificate)
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                Mandatory: Aadhar, PAN, passport size photograph
                            </li>
                        </ol>

                        <br/>

                        <p><strong>Looking forward to having you on board!</strong></p>

                        <p><strong>For <t t-out="object.company_id.name"/></strong></p>

                    </div>
                    <div style="margin-top: 40px; font-family: Arial;">

                        <!-- Title -->
                        <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline;">
                            <strong>ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE</strong>
                        </h3>

                        <br/>

                        <!-- Content -->
                        <p style="text-align: justify; line-height: 1.6;">
                            I have read and understood all the terms and conditions of my internship, and I do hereby agree
                            with all terms and shall abide by all general rules of internship which are now or may be in force,
                            and accordingly I accept my internship with you.
                        </p>

                        <br/><br/>

                        <!-- Signature -->
                        <p style="margin-top: 40px;">
                            _________________________
                        </p>
                        <p>(Signature)</p>
                    </div>
                    <div style="margin-top: 40px; font-family: Arial;">

                        <!-- Title -->
                        <h3 style="text-align: center; text-decoration: underline;">
                            <strong>NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT</strong>
                        </h3>

                        <br/>

                        <!-- Content -->
                        <p>
                            This Non-Disclosure Agreement ("Agreement") is made and entered into
                            and effective from (“Effective Date”), at Chennai, India
                        </p>

                        <h3>
                            <strong>BY AND BETWEEN</strong>
                        </h3>

                        <p>
                            LS Devices Private Limited, a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 2073 and having
                            office at 2C, 1st Floor, Indiqube Marina, Developed Plot, South Phase, Guindy Industrial Estate,
                            Chennai – 600 062 (hereinafter referred to as the “Company”) which expression unless repugnant to
                            the context or meaning thereof shall be deemed to include its successors and permitted assigns of the First Part,
                        </p>


                    </div>
                </div>
            </field>
            <field name="lang">{{ object.employee_version_id.employee_id.lang }}</field>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>

